Alice Rondo-san.
آليس روندو-سان
Here!
!حاضرة
Chloe Aubert-san.
كلوي أوبيرت-سان
Here.
حاضرة
Okay, everyone's here.
حسناً، الجميع هنا
As I told you previously,
،كما أخبرتُكم سلفاً
I'll be leaving Freedom Academy at the end of the current term.
سأغادر أكاديميّة الحرّية في نهاية الفصل الدّراسي الحالي
Sensei...
...سينسي
Hey, don't look so sad.
لا تحزنوا
I'll come back to visit all the time.
سأعود للزيارة من وقت لآخر
Hmph. Don't bother.
لا تُتعب نفسك
Yeah! It'll be a relief to have you gone!
!أجل! سيرتاح بالنا إذا غادرت يا سينسي
What's with the tough act?
ما هذا الادّعاء المزيّف؟
You guys just can't be honest with yourselves.
أنتما غير صادقين مع نفسيكما
Rimuru-sensei, you really will come visit, right?
ريمورو-سينسي، ستأتي للزيارة حقّاً، صحيح؟
Yeah, of course.
أجل، بالطبع
That said, we still have more than a month left until then.
رغم ذلك، ما زال أمامنا أكثر من شهر حتّى يحين ذلك
Also, you guys still have your finals to get through first,
وأيضاً ما زال أمامكم الامتحانات النّهائية ،لاجتيازها أولاً
so you'd better study hard!
!لذا حريّ بكم أن تدرسوا بجدّ
Ugh, finals?
الامتحانات النهائيّة؟
Rimuru-sensei, I'm here.
ريمورو-سينسي، أنا هنا
Oh, time for Tiss-sensei's class.
حان وقت درس تيس-سينسي
Come on in.
تفضّلي بالدخول
You guys better not make any trouble for Tiss-sensei, you hear?
حريّ بكم ألّا تسبّبوا المتاعب لتيس-سينسي، مفهوم؟
We wouldn't make any trouble.
مُحال أن نسبّب المتاعب
Tiss-sensei traveled to Guratol with us.
سافرت تيس-سينسي معنا إلى غوراتول
We have a pretty tight bond with her now.
رابطنا متين معها الآن
Yes, they're all great kids.
أجل، جميعهم أطفال رائعون
Great kids, huh?
أطفال رائعون؟
Okay, Tiss-sensei, they're all yours.
حسناً يا تيس-سينسي، أتركهم لكِ
Sure.
حسناً
What're you going to do, Rimuru-sensei?
ماذا ستفعل يا ريمورو-سينسي؟
Take a nap or something, I bet.
متأكّدة أنّه سيأخذ قيلولة أو ما شابه
Alice-kun, despite appearances, I have quite a lot of work to do!
،آليس-كن، بخلافِ ما يوحي به مظهري لديّ الكثير من الأعمال لأقوم بها
Until next time, everyone!
!ألقاكم لاحقاً جميعاً
See you later, Rimuru-sensei!
!ريمورو-سينسي، إلى اللّقاء
All right, let's start class.
حسناً، لنبدأ الدرس
Yes, ma'am!
!حاضر
Looks like she's getting along pretty well with them.
يبدو أنّها تنسجم بشكل جيّد معهم
Yes.
أجل
I guess this means I can count on Tiss-sensei to take over for me.
أعتقد هذا يعني أنّني أستطيع الاعتماد على تيس-سينسي في تولّي زمام الأمور
Well, then...
...إذاً
Yes, I'm very busy.
أجل، أنا مشغول جداً
Not only do I have the kids of Freedom Academy to look after,
،ليس على عاتقي الاهتمام بأطفال أكاديميّة الحرّية فقط
but I also have lots to do for Tempest, our nation of monsters.
بل على عاتقي أيضاً الكثير من الأعمال لتيمبيست، دولة الوحوش
Which means
معنى ذلك
the Spatial Movement skill I got by analyzing that air spirit sure is coming in handy.
مهارة الحركة المكانيّة التي حصلتُ عليها من خلال تحليل روح الهواء تلك تأتي أُكُلَها حقّاً
Yep, looks like another peaceful day in Tempest.
أجل، يبدو كيوم هادئ آخر في تيمبيست
I'm Rimuru Tempest, and I'm a slime.
اسمي ريمورو تيمبيست، وأنا هُلام
When I was a human, I was stabbed in a random attack,
،عندما كنتُ بشريّاً، طُعِنتُ بهجوم عشوائيّ
and I thought I had died...
...وظننتُ نفسي ميّتاً
but I reincarnated in this world as a slime.
لكن خُلِقتُ من جديد في هذا العالم كهُلام
I became friends with the Storm Dragon, Veldora...
...أصبحتُ صديقاً لتنّين العاصفة، فيلدورا
I built a nation of monsters...
...بنيتُ دولةً من الوحوش
And I fought to protect everyone in it.
وقاتلتُ لحماية الجميع فيها
Shizu-san's lingering regret...
...حسرة شيزو-سان طويلة الأمد
was those kids,
،كانت أولئك الأطفال
and I succeeded in saving them.
ونجحتُ في إنقاذهم
Now we can rest easy.
والآن يمكننا أن نسترخي
My time as a teacher is almost over now.
وقتي كمدرّس قد انتهى تقريباً
There sure have been lots of ups and downs,
،مررتُ بكثير من المطبّات
and a lot of pretty tough times, but now...
...وواجهتُ العديد من الأوقات العصيبة جدّاً، لكن الآن
You know, Ranga, I hope this peace will last forever.
آمل أن يدوم هذا السّلام للأبد يا رانغا
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
ذلك الوقت الذي خُلقت فيه من جديد كهُلام
Episode 25:  Rimuru's Busy Life
الحلقة 25: حياة ريمورو المزدحمة بالأعمال
I got involved in a bit of a mess with the Demon Lord Carrion,
أقحمتُ نفسي في فوضى مع سيّد ،الشّياطين كاريون
but then we signed a non-aggression pact, ending all hostilities between us.
لكن بعدها وقّعنا معاهدة عدم اعتداء لننهي العداوة بيننا
Then I accepted Carrion's proposal
ثمّ قبلتُ اقتراح كاريون
that the Jura Tempest Federation and the Animal Kingdom of Eurazania
وهو أن يعمل كُل من اتّحاد جورا تيمبيست ومملكة الحيوان يورازانيا
Jura Tempest Federation
اتّحاد جورا تيمبيست
Animal Kingdom of Eurazania
مملكة الحيوان يورازانيا
should each send out delegations to the other country.
على إرسال وفد لبعضهما الآخر
I appointed Benimaru to lead our delegation,
،عيّنتُ بينيمارو لقيادة وفدنا
with Rigur as his assistant.
بوجود ريغور مساعداً له
Rigur has grown into such a fine man!
!نضج ريغور وأصبح رجلاً حقيقياً
Today is the momentous day upon which our delegation departs,
،اليوم هو اليوم المهمّ الذي يغادر فيه وفدنا
and I'm back in Tempest to see them off.
وعدتُ إلى تيمبيست لأودّعه
Hmm, not bad.
لا بأس
Urgh... This shape is kinda hard to hold...
...هذا الشّكل من الصّعب قليلاً الحفاظ عليه
Great Rimuru, thank you for waiting.
ريمورو-ساما، شكراً لك على الانتظار
We've selected some ceremonial outfits for you to choose from.
انتقينا بعض الملابس الاحتفاليّة لتختار منها
Th-Thanks!
!شـ-شكراً
I guess I'll try them on right now.
أظنّني سأجرّبها الآن
I don't think this is quite right...
...لا أعتقد أنّ هذا مناسب
Then how about this one?
ما رأيك بهذا إذاً؟
Huh?! I don't know about this one, either...
...لا أعلم بشأن هذا أيضاً
I recommend this one!
!أوصي بهذا
You look fantastic, Great Rimuru!
!تبدو رائعاً يا ريمورو-ساما
It suits you perfectly!
!يلائمك بشكل مثاليّ
Listen, Shuna, Shion...
...اسمعا يا شونا وشيون
I think something more somber and respectful would be more appropriate.
أرى من الأنسب أن يكون لباساً قاتماً ومُوقّراً أكثر
More somber and respectful?
قاتم ومُوقّر أكثر؟
This delegation is important to the future of Tempest.
هذا الوفد مهمّ لمُستقبل تيمبيست
I want to send them off right.
أريد وداعه بشكل لائق
I see!
!هكذا إذاً
We do have some things that are somber and respectful.
لدينا أشياء قاتمة وأكثر وقاراً
Hey, it's starting.
سوف تبدأ
Great Rimuru!
!ريمورو-ساما
Great Rimuru looks amazing! Doesn't he, Gobzo?!
!يبدو ريمورو-ساما مذهلاً! أليس كذلك يا غوبزو؟
Y-You look great!
!تـ-تبدو رائعاً
So do you, Sir Gabiru!
!كذلك أنت يا غابيرو-ساما
Indeed!
!بالفعل
Not bad.
لا بأس
Master, you look splendid!
!مولايّ، تبدو بديعاً
Everyone, be silent!
!صمتاً جميعاً
I wish you all the best in carrying out this mission.
أتمنّى لكم كلّ التوفيق في تنفيذ هذه المهمّة
That's it?
فقط؟
Was that too short?!
!هل كانت مختصرة جدّاً؟
Okay, I'll add a bit more.
حسناً، سأضيف المزيد
Tempest has grown vastly more prosperous than it was before,
،ازدهرت تيمبيست بشكل كبير مقارنة بالسّابق
but it is still inexperienced as a nation.
لكن ما زالت أدنى من أن يُقال عنها دولة
If we can build a favorable relationship with Eurazania,
،إذا استطعنا بناء علاقات طيّبة مع يورازانيا
we can find ways to utilize the things that make their nation great,
يمكننا أن نستفيد من السُّبُل التي تجعل ،دولتهم عظيمة
which will help our own nation progress even further.
ما سيُساهم في إحراز دولتنا تيمبيست مزيداً من التقدّم
However...
...لكن
The Eastern Plains
نهر أميلد
The Demon Lord Carrion, ruler of Eurazania,
جبال كوشا
The Western Provinces
مملكة الحيوان يورازانيا
Tempest
دولة فولبروسيا المُجنّحة
Winged Nation of Fulbrosia
السّهول الشرقيّة
Animal Kingdom of Eurazania
الأقاليم الغربيّة
Kusha Mountains
،سيّد الشّياطين كاريون، حاكم يورازانيا
Ameld River
تيمبيست
also known as the Beastmaster, is a hardcore militant type.
والمعروف أيضاً بزعيم الوحوش، هو من النّوع العدوانيّ
He might be thinking, "Power is everything!"
"!لعلّه يقول لنفسه، "القوّة تعني كلّ شيء
If it looks like a fight's about to break out, come straight back here.
،إذا بدا أنّ معركة على وشك أن تندلع عودوا مباشرة إلى هنا
Our goal is not to fight.
هدفنا ليس القتال
It's to find out if our nations can get along,
،بل لمعرفة ما إن كان بلدانا سينسجمان
or if we need to sever relations with them.
أو إذا كنّا بحاجة لقطع العلاقات معهم
Although this is for the good of Tempest,
،رغم أنّ هذا يصبّ في مصلحة تيمبيست
you don't need to force yourself to endure any more than necessary.
ليس عليكم إجبار أنفسكم على تحمّل ما هو فوق طاقتكم
I'm counting on you!
!أعتمد عليكم
Yes, sir!
!حاضر
Great Rimuru! I'm so moved!
!ريمورو-ساما! أنا متأثّر جداً
There, there...
...مهلاً، مهلاً
I should be the one going out there, to be honest.
للأمانة، أنا من ينبغي أن يذهب إلى هناك
No, until we confirm that it is safe,
،لا، ما لم نتأكّد من سلامة ذلك
I believe you should refrain from entering a Demon Lord's domain.
أرى أنّك ينبغي أن تحجم عن دخول مجال سيّد شياطين
I will discern with my own eyes whether or not the Demon Lord Carrion can be trusted.
سأميّز بأمّ عيني ما إن كان سيّد الشّياطين كاريون شخصاً موثوقاً
Thanks.
شكراً
Remember, whatever you do, don't go picking a fight.
تذكّر، مهما فعلتم، لا تفتعلوا مشكلة
No need to worry.
لا حاجة للقلق
So reliable! Benimaru's really grown up!
!مؤتمن جدّاً! لقد نضج بينيمارو حقّاً
Good luck to you guys, too, Rigur.
حظّاً سعيداً لكم أيضاً يا ريغور
Thank you. I will gain as much experience as I can.
شكراً. سأكتسب أكبر قدر ممكن من الخبرة
We'll be on our way now.
سنغادر الآن
Have fun, you guys!
!استمتعوا جميعاً
Take care!
!بالتوفيق
Good luck!
!حظّاً سعيداً
Be safe, Brother!
!رافقتك السّلامة يا أخي
Good luck, everyone!
!حظّاً طيّباً لكم جميعاً
The first steps toward hope for our future, huh?
الخطوات الأولى نحو الأمل لمستقبلنا؟
Here's hoping we can establish formal diplomatic relations
آمل هنا أن نتمكّن من تأسيس علاقات دبلوماسيّة رسميّة
and help both of our nations grow even more.
والمساعدة في تنمية البلدين أكثر فأكثر
Thus the first delegation from our nation set out on its way.
وهكذا شدّ الوفد الأوّل من بلدنا الرّحال
And we have to get things ready here at home to welcome Eurazania's delegation, too.
وعلينا تجهيز الأمور هنا في الدّيار للترحيب بوفد يورازانيا أيضاً
Good, good. Looks like the reception hall will be ready in time.
جيّد، جيّد. يبدو أنّ صالة الاستقبال ستصبح جاهزة في الوقت
How are the chefs doing?
ما أخبار الطبّاخين؟
Just fine.
جيّدة
Princess Shuna is teaching them.
الأميرة شونا تعلّمهم
They're all quick learners and coming along well.
جميعهم يتعلّمون بسرعة وينسجمون معاً
Yes... I think it could use just a bit more salt.
أجل... أعتقد يحتاج لمزيد من الملح
As for the reception hall waiting staff,
،بالنسبة لطاقم الانتظار في قاعة الاستقبال
Vesta is giving them guidance.
فيستا يوجّههم
I guess proper etiquette is kind of his forte.
أعتقد أنّ آداب السّلوك هي اختصاصه
We can always count on an actual noble.
يمكننا دوماً الاعتماد على نبيل حقيقيّ
And, um... also...
...و... أيضاً
The date for your visit to the Armed Nation of Dwargon has been set.
تاريخ زيارتك لدولة دوارغون المُسلّحة قد تمّ تحديده
Oh, yeah. I need to see King Gazel in person
تذكّرت. عليّ رؤية الملك غازيل شخصيّاً
to thank him again for establishing diplomatic relations with Tempest.
لأشكره ثانية على تأسيس علاقات دبلوماسيّة مع تيمبيست
He's probably not too happy with Milim's involvement in the Charybdis incident,
إنّه على الأرجح غير راضٍ عن تدخّل ميليم ،بحادثة كاريبديس
so I need to explain that, too.
لذا عليّ شرح ذلك أيضاً
Treyni-san!
!تريني-سان
Greetings, Great Rimuru.
تحياتي يا ريمورو-ساما
What brings you here? Has something happened?
لماذا أتيتِ إلى هنا؟ هل حدث شيء؟
Yes.
أجل
The delegation from the Animal Kingdom of Eurazania has entered the Great Forest of Jura.
الوفد من مملكة الحيوان يورازانيا قد دخل غابة جورا العظيمة
I wanted to inform you.
أردتُ إبلاغكم
Ah, so they're almost here.
اقتربوا من هنا إذاً
They should arrive here in Tempest within five days.
ينبغي أن يصل إلى هنا في تيمبيست في غضون خمسة أيّام
Thanks for letting me know!
!شكراً على إبلاغي بذلك
It was the least I could do.
كان ذلك أقلّ ما يمكنني فعله
Also, it is likely that they will arrive before the delegation does.
وأيضاً من المُرجّح أن يصلوا قبل وصول الوفد
"They"?
يصلوا"؟"
Yes, the champion's...
...أجل، أقصد البطل
It's getting dark. Let's go home.
سيخيّم اللّيل. لنعد إلى المنزل
Okay!
!حسناً
How cute!
!ما أظرفه
Don't move!
!لا تتحرّكي
Youm and his buddies.
يوم ورفاقه
They used to be a gang of ruffians,
،كانوا عصابة مجرمين
but I had them become the champions who defeated the Orc Lord in our place.
لكن كنتُ قد جعلتُهم يصبحون الأبطال الذين هزموا سيّد الأورك بدلاً منّا
Wow...
...مذهل
If it got out that we defeated the Orc Lord,
،إذا تبيّن أنّنا نحن من هزمنا سيّد الأورك
it would just make humans wary of us.
فذلك سيجعل البشر يحترسون منّا
Are you all right?
هل أنتِ بخير؟
Y-Yes... Thank you so much.
أ-أجل... شكراً جزيلاً لك
Um... Thank you.
المعذرة... شكراً لك
Better be careful. There are some nasty monsters around here.
من الأفضل أن تتوخّي الحذر. هناك بعض الوحوش البغيضة في المنطقة
Your sword is so cool!
!سيفك غاية في الرّوعة
I know, right?
حقّاً؟
I had it made in a nation of good monsters called Tempest that's just ahead.
صنعته لي دولةٌ من الوحوش الطيّبين تُدعى تيمبيست وتقع على مقربة من هنا
They're traveling around telling people everywhere that we're friendly monsters.
يسافرون من مكان لآخر يخبرون كلّ الناس أنّنا وحوش مُسالمون
And from then on...
...ومن هذه اللّحظة
I continued to keep busy every day...
...ظللتُ منشغلاً كلّ يوم
right up until the day we welcomed the delegation from Eurazania.
حتّى أتى اليوم الذي رحّبنا فيه بالوفد من يورازانيا
Wow, this is good.
هذا لذيذ
It really is. I've never had it before.
بالفعل. لم يسبق أن تناولتُ مثيلاً له
Right? It's called brandy.
حقّاً؟ يُدعى براندي
Brandy, you say?
اسمه براندي؟
I made it as a special treat since we have guests visiting.
أعددتُه كهديّة خاصّة لاستقبال ضيوفنا
Oh, yeah? Guests?
حقّاً؟ ضيوف؟
Yep. The Demon Lord Carrion's delegation is arriving tomorrow.
أجل. سيصل وفد سيّد الشّياطين كاريون غداً
Did you do that on purpose?!
!هل فعلتم ذلك عمداً؟
The Demon Lord Carrion?! How the hell did that happen?!
!سيّد الشّياطين كاريون؟! كيف حدث ذلك؟
Well, it's a long story...
...في الواقع، إنّها قصّة طويلة
This feels so nice.
هذا شعور رائع
I see.
هكذا إذاً
So it's our chance to establish diplomatic relations.
هذه فرصتنا لتأسيس علاقات دبلوماسيّة
I get it.
فهمت
A Demon Lord, though? Really?
لكن سيّد شياطين؟ حقّاً؟
Sounds like that's gonna be one scary delegation.
يبدو أنّه سيكون وفداً مُخيفاً
I don't know about that. The goal isn't to fight.
لا أدري بشأن ذلك. ليس هدفنا القتال
But you sent Benimaru just in case the unforeseen happens, right?
لكنّك أرسلت بينيمارو تحسّباً لحدوث ما هو غير متوقّع، صحيح؟
Wouldn't they have the same idea?
ألن تنتابهم نفس الفكرة؟
If they do, it doesn't matter.
إن انتابتهم، فهذا غير مهمّ
I don't want to make a wrong move and waste this chance.
لا أريد أن أتّخذ أي خطوة خاطئة وأفوّت هذه الفرصة
Yeah, I guess not.
أجل، معك حقّ
You guys better not pick any fights with the delegates, either.
حريّ بكم ألّا تفتعلوا أي مشكلة مع أعضاء الوفد أيضاً
Hey, c'mon, Master. My boys and I aren't complete morons.
على رسلِك يا سيّدي. أنا وفتياني لسنا حمقى إلى هذه الدّرجة
Right?
صحيح؟
You said it.
تماماً
That's good, then.
هذا جيّد إذاً
By the way, Hakurou was hoping to see you.
بالمناسبة، كان هاكورو يأمل رؤيتكم
The master?!
!المعلّم؟
He wanted to make sure you haven't gotten rusty.
أراد أن يتأكّد من أنّ مستواكم لم يتراجع
Well, that sobered me right up.
جعلني ذلك أصحو حقّاً
Then, the next day...
...ثمّ في اليوم التّالي
Here they come.
ها قد أتوا
Horse-drawn carriages?
عربات أحصنة؟
No, those are tigers... Tiger-drawn carriages?
لا، تلك نمور... عربات نمور؟
They look like war chariots.
تبدو كعربات حرب
They're no big deal.
ليست بالأمر الجلل
In the face of your mighty power, that doesn't even work as a bluff.
أمام قوّتك العظيمة، تُعدّ هذه نكرة
Wait, wait, wait, Shion-san! They're definitely a big deal!
!لحظة، لحظة، لحظة يا شيون-سان !بل هم بالأمر الجلل
All those fancy decorations have no purpose in combat.
كلّ هذه التزيينات المزخرفة تعني أنّ لا نيّة لهم للقتال
Wait, wait, wait, Shion-san!
!لحظة، لحظة، لحظة يا شيون-سان
We're not talking about combat here!
!نحن لا نتحدّث عن القتال هنا
It is a pleasure to meet you,
،سررتُ بلقائك
leader of the Jura Tempest Federation, Rimuru Tempest.
يا قائد اتّحاد جورا تيمبيست، ريمورو تيمبيست
I am Albis, the Golden Serpent,
،أنا ألبيس، الثّعبان الذهبيّ
Animal Kingdom of Eurazania  Three Beastketeers The Golden Serpent  Albis
مملكة الحيوان يورازانيا    الفرسان الوحوش الثّلاثة الثّعبان الذهبيّ آلبيس
one of the Demon Lord Carrion's Three Beastketeers.
إحدى الفرسان الوحوش الثّلاثة التّابعين لسيّد الشّياطين كاريون
Wow, he sent his highest-ranking subordinates?
مذهل، أرسل أتباعه الأعلى شأناً؟
You gotta be kidding!
!هذا هراء
I came along 'cause I wondered what kind of monster the leader of Tempest was,
أتيتُ لأنّني تساءلتُ ما طبيعة ،قائد تيمبيست الوحش هذا
Animal Kingdom of Eurazania  Three Beastketeers The White Tiger Claw  Suphia
فيتبيّن أنّك مجرّد هُلام صغير جبان؟
and you're just a wussy, little slime?
مملكة الحيوان يورازانيا    الفرسان الوحوش الثّلاثة مِخلب النّمر الأبيض صوفيا
If you wanna screw with us, you can only take it so far!
إذا أردت أن تعبث معنا، فعليك أن تلزم حدودك
Wow, that one looks pretty strong, too.
تبدو هذه قويّة جدّاً أيضاً
Stand down, Suphia.
اهدئي يا صوفيا
You may as well be slinging mud directly onto Lord Carrion's face.
قد تسيئين لسمعة مولايّ كاريون بشكل مُباشر هكذا
Oh, shut up, Albis. You can't order me around.
اصمتي يا آلبيس. لا يمكنكِ أن تأمريني
Besides, Dwarves are one thing,
،وأيضاً، بغضّ النّظر عن الأقزام
but humans, too?
لكن بشر أيضاً؟
Anyone who pals around with puny, insolent, cowardly humans
أي أحد يرافق البشر الجبناء الوقحين التّافهين
is a disgrace to all monsters!
!هو عار على كلّ الوحوش
That's quite the take.
يا له من كلام
Youm here is my friend,
،يوم هنا هو صديقي
as well as a fellow student under the same master who taught me.
وكذلك تلميذ زميل تحت جناح نفس المعلّم الذي علّمني
Yeah? So what?
نعم؟ وماذا في ذلك؟
Hey, Youm...
...يوم
It bugs you to know she just made fun of you, doesn't it?
يزعجك أن تعلم أنّها سخرت منك للتو، أليس كذلك؟
Why don't you show her what you can do? I'll allow it.
لمَ لا تريها ما يمكنك فعله؟ سأسمح بذلك
Whoa, hang on! Weren't we gonna be peaceful about this?!
!تمهّل! ألم نتّفق أن نكون مسالمين حيال هذا؟
I wasn't planning to start any fights,
،لم أكن أنوي البدء بأي قتال
but if the other side does, that's another matter.
لكن إذا فعل الطرف الآخر ذلك، فتلك مسألة أخرى
Oh? You wanna play, human?
أتريد أن تلعب أيّها البشريّ؟
Uh, I...
...أنا
Go get 'er, boss!
!نَل منها يا زعيم
We can't let her make us look like losers!
!لن نسمح لها بأن تجعلنا نبدو فاشلين
Please do the honors, Youm!
!من فضلِك أدِّ الواجب يا يوم
All right, fine.
حسنٌ إذاً
Master, be sure to clean up the mess when I'm done, okay?
سيّدي، اِحرص على إزالة القذارة عندما أنتهي، اتّفقنا؟
Hah! You're asking a slime to clean up the mess?
أتطلب من هُلام أن يزيل القذارة؟
Don't make me laugh!
!أنت تُضحكني
Sure, I'll take care of... it?
بالتأكيد، سأتولّى... ذلك؟
Um... Shion-san?
شـ-شيون-سان؟
All she's done since she arrived is hurl insults toward you.
كلّ ما فعلته منذ وصولها هو توجيه الإهانات لك
I've put up with it all this time,
،تحمّلتُ الأمر طوال هذا الوقت
but it looks like there was never any need to!
!لكن يبدو أنّه لم يكن هناك أي حاجة لذلك
Wha... um...
...ما... المعذرة
It's me you'll be fighting.
أنا من ستقاتلينها
You wanna fight bare-handed, eh?
أتريدين مُقاتلتي بيدين مجرّدتين؟
Sounds fun!
!يبدو هذا ممتعاً
Is Shion gonna be okay?
هل ستكون شيون بخير؟
She's fighting on her opponent's terms, without her sword.
تقاتل وفق شروط خصمها، بلا سيفها
Don't worry, Great Rimuru.
لا تقلق يا ريمورو-ساما
Shion is almost as strong as my brother.
شيون بقوّة أخي تقريباً
R-Really?
حـ-حقّاً؟
Honestly, what are we going to do with that Suphia?
عجباً، ماذا سنفعل بشأن صوفيا تلك؟
Grucius.
غروشيس
Go and deal with that human.
اذهب وتعامل مع ذاك البشريّ
Just because I'm the runt in the Beastketeers,
،فقط لكوني الحيوان الأضعف من بين الفرسان الثّلاثة
Beast King's Beastketeers  Runt Grucius
الحيوان الأضعف من بين الفرسان الوحوش الثّلاثة غروشيس
I have to fight a human?
عليّ مقاتلة بشريّ؟
Fine, I'll play with you...
...حسناً، سألعب معك
human.
أيّها البشريّ
Great. Thanks.
عظيم. شكراً
Man, Youm's pretty good.
يا للهول! يوم بارع جدّاً
Grucius is a majin, and they're actually on even footing.
غروشيس هو من الماجين، ومستواهما مُتقارب بعض الشيء
Yes, he's fighting magnificently.
أجل، إنّه يقاتل بعظَمة
Hakurou's training is really paying off!
!تدريب هاكورو يُثمِر حقّاً
Damn, boss, not bad!
!تبّاً يا زعيم، أنت قويّ
That's a champion for ya!
!هكذا يكون الأبطال
I wasn't expecting you to be this much fun!
!لم أتوقّع أن تكوني مُمتِعة إلى هذا الحدّ
Don't underestimate me, Lycanthrope.
لا تستهيني بي أيّتها المستذئبة
The power of a Kijin can rend the heavens and shatter the earth!
!قوّة الكيجين قد تمزّق السّماء وتحطّم الأرض
I'll show you that right now!
!سأريكِ ذلك في الحال
Great! Show me!
!عظيم! أريني
Entertain me even more!
!متّعيني أكثر
Thus, immediately after the delegation from Eurazania arrived,
،وهكذا، بعد وصول الوفد من يورازانيا مباشرة
a ferocious battle broke out.
اندلعت معركة عنيفة
Of course, I was the one who instigated it.
وبالطبع، كنتُ أنا من أشعلها
Next time, "Trade with the Animal Kingdom."
"الحلقة القادمة، "تجارة مع مملكة الحيوان
Trade with the Animal Kingdom
تجارة مع مملكة الحيوان